{
    "id": "Covid-19_158",
    "claim": "It is very interesting to follow certain Telegram channels since there is no censorship in that social network. One of the most interesting channels you can follow right now is that of Dr. Luis de Benito since, with his usual courage, Benito publishes through this channel what the vast majority of doctors do not dare to say. We invite you to read one of your latest publications and to follow the new and interesting publications you make. If you want to know the truth about the virus and vaccines, you can follow the doctor's channel. of Benito by clicking on this link. 1. National politics begins to move with the hand of some Autonomous Communities. There are those who want to wake up from the lethargy, attention to the next political events. 2. YouTube returns the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us: neither did it say why it was removed nor why it was replaced. He didn't even give me time to send the appeal. The strength of many few. 3. That being the case, I understand that there will be no veto to have direct this Tuesday. Let's see what I can tell you about what we're finding out. And between it.. (attentive)..4. As I cannot say, the Astra Zeneca vaccine has been suspended in 10 European Union countries. Common and severe thrombosis problems, including. In Spain this product continues to be put among teachers and members of the FAS and FF. SS. I think it's a serious irresponsibility. It gives the impression that fear can be more than common sense. 5. In Spain, 1000 people died within 7 days of receiving a dose of COVID vaccine. Still “investigating” (ignoring) if there is a relationship. The media doesn't mention it. 6. Popular initiatives to awaken people from fraud are increasing. Circulates a trailer of a documentary in which I appear among many others for the cause 7. Other more modest and more local initiatives arise in many places: editing stories, messages by iVoxx, video clips, or meetings like the one we will have in Guadalajara (from Spain, not Mexico) on Saturday 20 that I enclose you below. We must all be a focus of irradiation of joy and positive vision. 8. Some of you have suggested that you be able to open the comments on this channel.. but it would be to fret with the sense of the channel because 4 thousand and beak commenting.. you imagine. I answer many of the comments you make on YouTube channels and blog and also by private. 9. This weekend I have meetings with immunologist colleagues about the current vaccines and the new ones.. It doesn't look flattering at all. Most seem to deteriorate the immune system's response in the medium term, weaken it and make it less effective. My advice remains that no vaccine is needed for COVID. 10. You see, we're still growing in this canal. Personally I speak with the same sense of responsibility for 4 people as for 4000. But I do not hide from you that the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram attracts the attention of the media and professional associations because it is an unprecedented social phenomenon. If this month we reach 40. 000 subscribers, they'll call me a chapter on some national network. The Power of a Strong Group. If so, I'd talk to everyone about what I'm telling you here. If each of us invite 10 contacts from our WhatsApp is simple. One last warning I said live: none of my media activities and networks are monetized. If someone asks you for money for a cause in my name, it's a lie. Of course, anyone who organizes an activity that has a cost and is voluntary (such as Guadalajara) has to have a cost but it is never a cost. I don't ask for money for any cause, at least for the time being. If I changed the stage, I'd tell you. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.eldiestro.es",
    "date": "15/03/2021",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "It is very interesting to follow certain Telegram channels since the immune system's response in Telegram .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why is it interesting to follow certain Telegram channels?",
                    "answer": "the immune system's response"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of using certain Telegram channels?",
                    "score": 0.7688,
                    "answers": "to follow certain Telegram channels|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the functions of Telegram channels?",
                    "score": 0.7579,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tto|aux\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the Telegram channels?",
                    "score": 0.7566,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\tcertain Telegram channels|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the immune system's response in Telegram?",
                    "score": 0.7121,
                    "answers": "since the immune system 's response in Telegram|prep\tthe immune system 's|poss\tthe immune system 's response in Telegram|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Telegram and the immune system?",
                    "score": 0.6647,
                    "answers": "on 15/03/2021|prep\tIt|nsubj\tthat It is very interesting to follow certain Telegram channels since the immune system 's response in Telegram|ccomp\tvery|advmod\tcertain|amod\t's|case"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "One the immune system's response the most the immune system's response channels you can follow right now is that of Dr. Luis de Benito since, with usual courage, Dr. Luis de Benito publishes through that of Dr. Luis de Benito what the vast majority of doctors do not dare to say.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who publishes through that of Dr. Luis de Benito?",
                    "answer": "Dr. Luis de Benito"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Dr. Luis de Benito write about the immune system's response channels?",
                    "score": 0.8188,
                    "answers": "that of Dr. Luis de Benito|attr\tthat of Dr. Luis de Benito|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Dr. Luis de Benito's position on immune system response channels?",
                    "score": 0.7269,
                    "answers": "immune|amod\timmune|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We invite My to read one of latest the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Eldiestro say on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long does it take to read one of latest the power to gather in a short time?",
                    "score": 0.5663,
                    "answers": "in a short time|prep\ta short time|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people are on the Telegram platform?",
                    "score": 0.5301,
                    "answers": "a large number of people|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the power of Telegram?",
                    "score": 0.5098,
                    "answers": "one of latest the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the functions of Telegram?",
                    "score": 0.5051,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\twww.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that We invite My to read one of latest the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram|ROOT\ton 15/03/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tWe|nsubj\tMy|dobj\tto|aux\tlatest|amod\tthe|det\tlatest the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram|pobj\tto|aux\tto assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram|acl\ta|det\tshort|amod\ta|det\tlarge|amod\tof people|prep\tpeople|pobj\ton a platform such as Telegram|prep\ta|det\tsuch|amod\tsuch as Telegram|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Telegram?",
                    "score": 0.4738,
                    "answers": "a platform such as Telegram|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram the truth about the virus and vaccines, you can follow Dr. Luis de Benito channel.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Whose channel can you follow to learn more about the virus and vaccines?",
                    "answer": "Dr. Luis de Benito"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Dr. Luis de Benito's position on vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.6965,
                    "answers": "about the virus and vaccines|prep\tthe virus and vaccines|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people can follow Dr. Luis de Benito channel?",
                    "score": 0.6314,
                    "answers": "that the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram the truth about the virus and vaccines , you can follow Dr. Luis de Benito channel|ccomp\tof people|prep\tpeople|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the truth about the virus and vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.6217,
                    "answers": "the truth about the virus and vaccines|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the power to gather in a short time?",
                    "score": 0.5352,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram the truth about the virus and vaccines , you can follow Dr. Luis de Benito channel|ROOT\tin a short time|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of Telegram?",
                    "score": 0.5287,
                    "answers": "to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram the truth about the virus and vaccines|acl\ton a platform such as Telegram|prep\ta platform such as Telegram|pobj\tsuch as Telegram|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "of Dr. Luis de Benito by clicking on this link.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did Eldiestro.es say was in contact with on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "Dr. Luis de Benito"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the link to Dr. Luis de Benito's website?",
                    "score": 0.7898,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Dr. Luis de Benito?",
                    "score": 0.7585,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that of Dr. Luis de Benito by clicking on this link|ROOT\ton 15/03/2021|prep\tthat of Dr. Luis de Benito|dobj\tof Dr. Luis de Benito|prep\tDr.|compound\tLuis|compound\tde|compound\tDr. Luis de Benito|pobj\tby clicking on this link|prep\tthis|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "National politics begins to move with the hand of some My Communities.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that National politics began to move with the hand of some My Communities?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between nationalism and politics?",
                    "score": 0.6782,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\ton 15/03/2021|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are My Communities?",
                    "score": 0.6271,
                    "answers": "of some My Communities|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "There are those who want to wake up from the lethargy, attention to the next political events.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that there are those who want to wake up from the lethargy?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are those who want to wake up from the lethargy, attention to political events?",
                    "score": 0.7351,
                    "answers": "who want to wake up from the lethargy , attention to the next political events|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of lethargy?",
                    "score": 0.7306,
                    "answers": "from the lethargy , attention to the next political events|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the next political events?",
                    "score": 0.7294,
                    "answers": "the next political events|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the political events in the United States?",
                    "score": 0.6566,
                    "answers": "political|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Spain returns the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us : neither did YouTube say why the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us My removed nor why the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us was replaced.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did www.eldiestro.es say on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "Spain returns the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Spain return on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the broadcast on Tuesday?",
                    "score": 0.6905,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\twww.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that Spain returns the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us : neither did YouTube say why the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us My removed nor why the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us was replaced|ROOT\tthe broadcast on Tuesday that censored us|dobj\ton Tuesday|prep\tneither did YouTube say why the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us My removed nor why the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us was replaced|conj\tthe broadcast on Tuesday that censored us|nsubjpass\ton Tuesday|prep\twhy the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us My removed nor why the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us was replaced|ccomp\tthe broadcast on Tuesday that censored us|nsubjpass\ton Tuesday|prep\twhy the broadcast on Tuesday that censored us was replaced|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "He didn't even give me time to send the appeal.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did Eldiestro say that he didn't even give me time to send the appeal?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How long did it take to send an appeal?",
                    "score": 0.8349,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that He did n't even give me time to send the appeal|ROOT\teven|advmod\tme|dative"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long did the appeal take to appeal?",
                    "score": 0.8151,
                    "answers": "n't|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the appeal that was sent?",
                    "score": 0.7125,
                    "answers": "on 15/03/2021|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the outcome of the appeal?",
                    "score": 0.7074,
                    "answers": "the appeal|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The strength of many few.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that the strength of many few was the strength of many few?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the strength of many few?",
                    "score": 0.6018,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThe|det\tof many few|prep\tmany|amod\tmany few|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "My this channel the case, me understand that there will be no this channel direct this Tuesday.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the case on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "this channel"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of this channel?",
                    "score": 0.6956,
                    "answers": "on 15/03/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tMy|dep\tthis|det\tthis channel|dep\tthe|det\tthis channel the case|dep\t,|punct\tme|nsubj\tthat|mark\tthere|expl\twill|aux\tthat there will be no this channel direct this Tuesday|ccomp\tno|det\tthis|det\tno this channel direct|attr\tdirect|amod\tthis|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the channel?",
                    "score": 0.6224,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "As me cannot say, the Astra Zeneca vaccine I been suspended in 10 European Union countries.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What vaccine was suspended in 10 European Union countries?",
                    "answer": "Astra Zeneca"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why was the Astra Zeneca vaccine suspended?",
                    "score": 0.8889,
                    "answers": "that As me can not say , the Astra Zeneca vaccine I been suspended in 10 European Union countries|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many European Union countries have suspended the Astra Zeneca vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.848,
                    "answers": "in 10 European Union countries|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Common and severe thrombosis problems, including.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that Common and severe thrombosis problems occurred?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are common and severe thrombosis problems?",
                    "score": 0.8635,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that Common and severe thrombosis problems , including|ROOT\tthat|mark\tCommon and severe|amod\tand|cc\tthat Common and severe thrombosis problems , including|dobj\t,|punct\tincluding|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the symptoms of severe thrombosis?",
                    "score": 0.8488,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is thrombosis?",
                    "score": 0.8355,
                    "answers": "thrombosis|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between common and severe thrombosis?",
                    "score": 0.8134,
                    "answers": "on 15/03/2021|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In Spain this product continues to be put among teachers and members of the FAS and FF.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that in Spain this product continues to be put among teachers and members of the FAS and FF?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many teachers and members of FAS and FF use the FAS products in Spain?",
                    "score": 0.7252,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that In Spain this product continues to be put among teachers and members of the FAS and FF|ROOT\tthis|det\tto|aux\tbe|auxpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the FAS and FF?",
                    "score": 0.5726,
                    "answers": "to be put among teachers and members of the FAS and FF|xcomp\tmembers of the FAS and FF|conj\tof the FAS and FF|prep\tthe FAS and FF|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "SS.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date was it announced by SS?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the SS stand for?",
                    "score": 0.5905,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that SS|ROOT\ton 15/03/2021|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the link between SS andldiestro?",
                    "score": 0.5687,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the SS?",
                    "score": 0.5263,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat SS|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It gives the impression that fear can be more than common sense.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the website say fear can be more than?",
                    "answer": "common sense"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How can fear be more than common sense?",
                    "score": 0.8624,
                    "answers": "can|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does fear say about common sense?",
                    "score": 0.8605,
                    "answers": "that It gives the impression that fear can be more than common sense|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does fear mean in common sense?",
                    "score": 0.8577,
                    "answers": "common|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of fear?",
                    "score": 0.7509,
                    "answers": "the impression that fear can be more than common sense|dobj\tthat fear can be more than common sense|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is fear?",
                    "score": 0.7463,
                    "answers": "fear|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In Spain, 1000 people died within 7 days of receiving a dose of COVID vaccine.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many people died within 7 days of receiving a dose of COVID vaccine?",
                    "answer": "1000"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many people died of the COVID vaccine in Spain in 2007?",
                    "score": 0.8708,
                    "answers": "1000 people|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Still “investigating” (ignoring) if there is a relationship.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did www.eldiestro.es say that still “investigating” (ignoring) if there is a relationship?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a man and woman?",
                    "score": 0.6509,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\twww.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that Still “ investigating ” ( ignoring ) if there is a relationship|ROOT\ton 15/03/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tStill|advmod\t“|punct\tthat Still “ investigating ” ( ignoring ) if there is a relationship|ccomp\t”|punct\t(|punct\tignoring|dep\t)|punct\tif|mark\tthere|expl\tif there is a relationship|ccomp\ta|det\ta relationship|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The media doesn't mention it.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did Eldiestro say that the media didn't mention it?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the media say about the media not mentioning it?",
                    "score": 0.7685,
                    "answers": "on 15/03/2021|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the media mention ofldiestro?",
                    "score": 0.6673,
                    "answers": "it|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the media's coverage of theeldiestro.es?",
                    "score": 0.6583,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that The media does n't mention it|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does the media say aboutldiestro.es?",
                    "score": 0.6434,
                    "answers": "The media|nsubj\tdoes|aux"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Popular initiatives to awaken people from fraud are increasing.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that Popular initiatives to awaken people from fraud are increasing?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What initiatives are being taken to awaken people from fraud?",
                    "score": 0.8903,
                    "answers": "Popular|amod\tPopular initiatives to awaken people from fraud|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many fraud victims are there each year?",
                    "score": 0.8504,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\twww.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that Popular initiatives to awaken people from fraud are increasing|ROOT\tthat|mark\tto|aux\tto awaken people from fraud|acl\tare|aux\tthat Popular initiatives to awaken people from fraud are increasing|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the current fraud rate in the USA?",
                    "score": 0.8286,
                    "answers": "on 15/03/2021|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Circulates a trailer of a documentary in which I appear among many others for the cause 7.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Eldiestro say on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "Circulates a trailer of a documentary in which I appear among many others for the cause 7"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the film 7?",
                    "score": 0.5653,
                    "answers": "that Circulates a trailer of a documentary in which I appear among many others for the cause 7|ccomp\ta trailer of a documentary in which I appear among many others for the cause 7|dobj\tof a documentary in which I appear among many others for the cause 7|prep\ta documentary in which I appear among many others for the cause 7|pobj\tfor the cause 7|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the film that was shown in the film 7?",
                    "score": 0.532,
                    "answers": "in which I appear among many others for the cause 7|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the cause of the video 7?",
                    "score": 0.5266,
                    "answers": "the cause 7|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Other more modest and more local initiatives arise in many places: editing stories, messages by iVoxx, video clips, or meetings like the one we will have in Guadalajara (from Spain, not Mexico) on Saturday 20 that I enclose you below.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What are some of the more modest and local initiatives?",
                    "answer": "editing stories, messages by iVoxx, video clips, or meetings like the one we will have in Guadalajara (from Spain, not Mexico) on Saturday 20"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many local initiatives are there in Guadalajara?",
                    "score": 0.6016,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that Other more modest and more local initiatives arise in many places : editing stories , messages by iVoxx , video clips , or meetings like the one we will have in Guadalajara ( from Spain , not Mexico ) on Saturday 20 that I enclose you below|ROOT\tthat Other more modest and more local initiatives arise in many places :|ccomp\tin many places|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is Guadalajara from?",
                    "score": 0.5906,
                    "answers": "Guadalajara ( from Spain , not Mexico )|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the meeting in Guadalajara on Saturday 20?",
                    "score": 0.5659,
                    "answers": "video clips , or meetings like the one we will have in Guadalajara ( from Spain , not Mexico ) on Saturday 20 that I enclose you below|conj\tmeetings like the one we will have in Guadalajara ( from Spain , not Mexico ) on Saturday 20 that I enclose you below|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the location of the meeting that iVoxx attended in Guadalajara?",
                    "score": 0.5544,
                    "answers": "from Spain , not Mexico|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between local initiatives and local initiatives?",
                    "score": 0.5234,
                    "answers": "more modest and more local|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We must all be a focus of irradiation of joy and positive vision.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that we must all be a focus of irradiation of joy and positive vision?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of irradiation of joy and positive vision?",
                    "score": 0.5956,
                    "answers": "on 15/03/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tWe|nsubj\tmust|aux\tall|dep\tthat We must all be a focus of irradiation of joy and positive vision|ccomp\ta|det\ta focus of irradiation of joy and positive vision|attr\tof irradiation of joy and positive vision|prep\tirradiation of joy and positive vision|pobj\tof joy and positive vision|prep\tjoy and positive vision|pobj\tand|cc\tpositive|amod\tpositive vision|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the quotes byldiestro.es?",
                    "score": 0.4888,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that We must all be a focus of irradiation of joy and positive vision|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Some of you have suggested that you be able to open the comments on this channel.. but it would be to fret with the sense of the channel because 4 thousand and beak commenting.. you imagine.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that some of you have suggested that you be able to open the comments on this channel?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What do you do when you see the comments on Eldiestro?",
                    "answer": "imagine"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many comments are there on the channel?",
                    "score": 0.6721,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\ton 15/03/2021|prep\tthe comments on this channel|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the ways to open the comments on the channel?",
                    "score": 0.6476,
                    "answers": "that you be able to open the comments on this channel|ccomp\tto open the comments on this channel|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the sense of the channel?",
                    "score": 0.5908,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that Some of you have suggested that you be able to open the comments on this channel .. but it would be to fret with the sense of the channel because 4 thousand and beak commenting .. you imagine|ROOT\tthat|mark\tSome of you|nsubj\tof you|prep\tyou|pobj\thave|aux\tthat Some of you have suggested that you be able to open the comments on this channel .. but it would be to fret with the sense of the channel because 4 thousand and beak commenting .. you imagine|ccomp\tthat|mark\tyou|nsubj\tto|aux\tthe|det\ton this channel|prep\tthis|det\tthis channel|pobj\t..|punct\tbut|cc\tit|nsubj\twould|aux\tit would be to fret with the sense of the channel because 4 thousand and beak commenting .. you imagine|conj\tto|aux\tto fret with the sense of the channel|xcomp\twith the sense of the channel|prep\tthe|det\tthe sense of the channel|pobj\tof the channel|prep\tthe|det\tthe channel|pobj\tbecause|mark\t4|compound\t4 thousand and beak|nsubj\tand|cc\tbeak|conj\tbecause 4 thousand and beak commenting ..|advcl\t..|punct\tyou|nsubj\tyou imagine|parataxis"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I answer many of the comments you make on YouTube channels and blog and also by private.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did eldiestro.es say on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "many of the comments you make on YouTube channels and blog"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many comments do you make on youtube channels and blog?",
                    "score": 0.6936,
                    "answers": "many of the comments you make on YouTube channels and blog|dobj\tof the comments you make on YouTube channels and blog|prep\tthe comments you make on YouTube channels and blog|pobj\tyou make on YouTube channels and blog|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many comments are made on youtube and blog?",
                    "score": 0.6521,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\tand|cc\tand|cc\talso|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between private and private comments?",
                    "score": 0.5377,
                    "answers": "and also by private|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "This weekend I have meetings with immunologist colleagues about the current vaccines and the new ones.. It doesn't look flattering at all.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did eldiestro.es say that I had meetings with immunologist colleagues about vaccines?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is it flattering or flattering to have meetings with immunologists about vaccines?",
                    "answer": "doesn't look flattering"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the new vaccines?",
                    "score": 0.8116,
                    "answers": "the new ones|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the current vaccines and new ones?",
                    "score": 0.7551,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\twww.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that This weekend I have meetings with immunologist colleagues about the current vaccines and the new ones ..|ROOT\ton 15/03/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tThis|det\tI|nsubj\tthat This weekend I have meetings with immunologist colleagues about the current vaccines and the new ones|ccomp\tmeetings with immunologist colleagues about the current vaccines and the new ones|dobj\twith immunologist colleagues|prep\timmunologist colleagues|pobj\tabout the current vaccines and the new ones|prep\tthe|det\tcurrent|amod\tthe current vaccines and the new ones|pobj\tand|cc\tthe|det\tnew|amod\t..|punct\tIt|nsubj\tdoes|aux\tn't|neg\tIt does n't look flattering at all|ROOT\tflattering|acomp\tat|advmod\tat all|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the job of an immunologist?",
                    "score": 0.6972,
                    "answers": "immunologist|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Most seem to deteriorate the immune system's response in the medium term, weaken it and make it less effective.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did eldiestro.es say about the immune system in the medium term?",
                    "answer": "deteriorate the immune system's response"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How effective is the immune system's response in the medium term?",
                    "score": 0.7838,
                    "answers": "on 15/03/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tto|aux\tthe|det\t's|case\tthe|det\tmedium|amod\t,|punct\tit|dobj\tand|cc\tit|nsubj\tless|advmod\tit less effective|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the effects of weakened immune systems?",
                    "score": 0.7648,
                    "answers": "weaken it and make it less effective|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process used to improve the immune system's response?",
                    "score": 0.7321,
                    "answers": "to deteriorate the immune system 's response in the medium term , weaken it and make it less effective|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the immune system and the human body?",
                    "score": 0.6773,
                    "answers": "the immune system 's|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the term used to describe the impact of the immune system on the medium term?",
                    "score": 0.6677,
                    "answers": "the medium term|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "My advice remains that no vaccine is needed for COVID.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is my advice for COVID?",
                    "answer": "no vaccine is needed"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What vaccines are needed for COVID?",
                    "score": 0.9135,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\twww.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that My advice remains that no vaccine is needed for COVID|ROOT\ton 15/03/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tthat My advice remains that no vaccine is needed for COVID|ccomp\tthat|mark\tno|det\tthat no vaccine is needed for COVID|ccomp\tfor COVID|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the COVID vaccine?",
                    "score": 0.8441,
                    "answers": "My|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is COVID?",
                    "score": 0.8034,
                    "answers": "COVID|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "You see, we're still growing in this canal.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did eldiestro.es say that we're still growing in this canal?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the current population of the Suez Canal?",
                    "score": 0.8392,
                    "answers": "that You see , we 're still growing in this canal|ccomp\tthis canal|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the growth of theldiestro.es?",
                    "score": 0.6982,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that You see , we 're still growing in this canal|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Personally I speak with the same sense of responsibility for 4 people as for 4000.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the sense of responsibility for 4 people that I spoke with on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "the same sense of responsibility for 4 people"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the website \"eldiestro.es\" do?",
                    "score": 0.577,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that Personally I speak with the same sense of responsibility for 4 people as for 4000|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people are there for each other?",
                    "score": 0.5745,
                    "answers": "for 4000|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the responsibilities of 4 people?",
                    "score": 0.5649,
                    "answers": "responsibility for 4 people|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between leadership and responsibility for 4 people?",
                    "score": 0.5553,
                    "answers": "same|amod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But I do not hide from you that the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram attracts the attention of the media and professional associations because it is an unprecedented social phenomenon.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that the power to assemble in a short time attracts the attention of the media and professional associations?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Eldiestro say on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram attracts the attention of the media and professional associations"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many people are on the Telegram platform?",
                    "score": 0.5554,
                    "answers": "to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of using Telegram?",
                    "score": 0.5519,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that But I do not hide from you that the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram attracts the attention of the media and professional associations because it is an unprecedented social phenomenon|ROOT\tthat the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram attracts the attention of the media and professional associations because it is an unprecedented social phenomenon|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the social phenomenon of Telegram?",
                    "score": 0.5178,
                    "answers": "an unprecedented social phenomenon|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the power to gather in a short time?",
                    "score": 0.4976,
                    "answers": "that But I do not hide from you that the power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram attracts the attention of the media and professional associations because it is an unprecedented social phenomenon|ccomp\tthe power to assemble in a short time a large number of people on a platform such as Telegram|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If this month we reach 40.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date did Eldiestro say that if we reach 40 in a month, we would reach 40 in a month?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the rate of unemployment in the United States?",
                    "score": 0.6117,
                    "answers": "that If this month we reach 40|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the current population ofldiestro.es?",
                    "score": 0.5281,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that If this month we reach 40|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "000 subscribers, they'll call me a chapter on some national network.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What will subscribers call me on a national network on 15/03/2021?",
                    "answer": "a chapter"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many subscribers does the network have?",
                    "score": 0.7994,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\twww.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that 000 subscribers , they 'll call me a chapter on some national network|ROOT\ton 15/03/2021|prep\tthat|mark\t000 subscribers|npadvmod\t,|punct\tthey|nsubj\t'll|aux\tthat 000 subscribers , they 'll call me a chapter on some national network|ccomp\tme|dobj\ta|det\ta chapter on some national network|oprd\ton some national network|prep\tsome|det\tnational|amod\tsome national network|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The Power of a Strong Group.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "On what date was The Power of a Strong Group announced?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the power of a strong group?",
                    "score": 0.7311,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\twww.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that The Power of a Strong Group|ROOT\ton 15/03/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tThe|det\tthat The Power of a Strong Group|ccomp\tof a Strong Group|prep\ta|det\tStrong|amod\ta Strong Group|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If each of us invite 10 contacts from our WhatsApp is simple.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many contacts can we invite from our WhatsApp?",
                    "answer": "invite 10 contacts"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How simple is it to invite 10 contacts from WhatsApp?",
                    "score": 0.7948,
                    "answers": "simple|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many contacts does each of us invite from WhatsApp?",
                    "score": 0.739,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\tthat|mark\tIf|mark\tof us|prep\tus|pobj\tour|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Whatsapp and WhatsApp?",
                    "score": 0.6172,
                    "answers": "on 15/03/2021|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "One last warning I said live: none of my media activities and networks are monetized.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "How many of my media activities are monetized?",
                    "answer": "none"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many media activities and networks are monetized?",
                    "score": 0.8102,
                    "answers": "that One last warning I said live : none of my media activities and networks are monetized|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Trump's media activities and networks?",
                    "score": 0.7405,
                    "answers": "none of my media activities and networks|nsubjpass\tmy media activities and networks|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between live and live media?",
                    "score": 0.6433,
                    "answers": "live|advmod"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If someone asks you for money for a cause in my name, it's a lie.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that if someone asks you for money for a cause in my name, it's a lie?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to ask for money for a cause?",
                    "score": 0.7852,
                    "answers": "If someone asks you for money for a cause in my name|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the money given to people for a cause in their name?",
                    "score": 0.6478,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that If someone asks you for money for a cause in my name , it 's a lie|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of a lie?",
                    "score": 0.6338,
                    "answers": "that If someone asks you for money for a cause in my name , it 's a lie|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Of course, anyone who organizes an activity that has a cost and is voluntary (such as Guadalajara) has to have a cost but it is never a cost.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who has to have a cost in Guadalajara?",
                    "answer": "anyone who organizes an activity that has a cost and is voluntary"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the cost of Guadalajara?",
                    "score": 0.7713,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj\ton 15/03/2021|prep\tthat has a cost and is voluntary|relcl\ta cost|dobj\tthat Of course , anyone who organizes an activity that has a cost and is voluntary ( such as Guadalajara ) has to have a cost but it is never a cost|ccomp\tto have a cost|xcomp\ta cost|dobj\tit is never a cost|conj\ta cost|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Guadalajara?",
                    "score": 0.7581,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es said on 15/03/2021 that Of course , anyone who organizes an activity that has a cost and is voluntary ( such as Guadalajara ) has to have a cost but it is never a cost|ROOT\tthat|mark\tOf|advmod\tOf course|advmod\t,|punct\tanyone who organizes an activity that has a cost and is voluntary ( such as Guadalajara )|nsubj\twho|nsubj\twho organizes an activity that has a cost and is voluntary ( such as Guadalajara )|relcl\tan|det\tan activity that has a cost and is voluntary ( such as Guadalajara )|dobj\tthat|nsubj\ta|det\tand|cc\tis voluntary|conj\tvoluntary|acomp\t(|punct\tsuch|amod\tsuch as Guadalajara|prep\t)|punct\tto|aux\ta|det\tbut|cc\tit|nsubj\tnever|neg\ta|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I don't ask for money for any cause, at least for the time being.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eldiestro.es say that I don't ask for money for any cause?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Mitt Romney's donations?",
                    "score": 0.7399,
                    "answers": "n't|neg\tat least|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How much money doesldiestro.es ask for?",
                    "score": 0.7294,
                    "answers": "for money|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If I changed the stage, I'd tell you.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did eldiestro.es say that if I changed the stage, I'd tell you about it?",
                    "answer": "15/03/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What would happen if a politician changed the stage?",
                    "score": 0.7777,
                    "answers": "If|mark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of how many people have changed their stage time since Trump took office?",
                    "score": 0.6986,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\t'd|aux\tyou|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the website \"eldiestro.es\"?",
                    "score": 0.5667,
                    "answers": "www.eldiestro.es|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}